Guide to the Poly Frame Rack RG.056
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Poly Archives Frame Rack
1848-2011
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.056
25 Cubic Feet
Scope and Contents
The Poly Frame Rack contains material from 1848 to 2011. This material includes photographs, portraits, plaques, proclamations, drawings, and diplomas. Shelf 1 and 5 include materials that are accessioned into the Herman Mark Papers, Shelf 2 includes materials that are accessioned into the Ernst Weber Papers, Shelf 6 includes materials that are accessioned into the Administrative Papers of the President and Chancellor George Bugliariello, and Shelf 5 and 8 include materials that are accessioned into the Jerry Hutlin Papers. The Poly Archives Frame Rack is located in the Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology.
- Series I: Shelf 1, 1959-1985
  - The Jabotinsky Centennial Medal, 1980-11-11 (Bin 1, Frame 1)
  - 30 Years of International Cellulose Research Limited, 1969 (Bin 1, Frame 2)
  - International Award in Plastics Science and Engineering, 1962 (Bin 1, Frame 3)
  - Tree Dedication Certificate, 1983 (Bin 1, Frame 4)
  - Journal of Polymer Research Replica Cover of Inaugural Issue, 1985 (Bin 1, Frame 5)
  - Family Crest, Undated (Bin 1, Frame 6)
  - German Certificate, 1970 (Bin 1, Frame 7)
  - Quarter Century Service Scroll, Undated (Bin 1, Frame 8)
  - Society of Plastics Engineers, Inc. Member Emeritus, 1959 (Bin 1, Frame 9)
  - Polymer Education Award, 1982 (Bin 1, Frame 10)
  - Honorary Membership to The Fiber Society, 1965 (Bin 1, Frame 11)
  - Division of Polymer Chemistry Award, 1982 (Bin 1, Frame 12)
  - 80th Birthday Plaque from Polytechnic Institute, 1975 (Bin 1, Frame 13)
  - Division of Cellulose Chemistry, 1959 (Bin 1, Frame 14)
  - The Seventh Annual Plastics Planning Conference Distinguished Speaker Plaque, 1981 (Bin 1, Frame 15)
  - Perkin Medal Award from the American Section of the Society of Chemical Industry, 1980 (Bin 1, Frame 16)
  - Bravery Medal in 1st World War for Most Decorated Officers, Undated (Bin 1, Frame 17)
- Series II: Shelf 2, 1934-2005
  - MRI Reunion to Honor our Friend and Colleague Ernst Weber, 1969-07-02 (Bin 2, Frame 1)
  - Society of the Sigma Chi, 1970-05-08 (Bin 2, Frame 2)
  - Gold Medal of Honor for Distinguished Service in Medicine from The Long Island College Hospital, 1967-03-11 (Bin 2, Frame 4)
  - American institute of Electrical Engineers Fellow, 1934-06-07 (Bin 2, Frame 5)
  - 75th Birthday Greeting from the Transportation Planning and Engineering Program at Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1976-01-20 (Bin 2, Frame 6)
  - Linton E. Grinter Distinguished Service Award, 1978-10-02 (Bin 2, Frame 7)
  - License to Practice Professional Engineering from the University of the State of New York Education Department, 1953-01-09 (Bin 2, Frame 8)
  - National Academy of Engineering Founding Members Diploma, 1964-12-10 (Bin 2, Frame 9)
  - American Institute of Electrical Engineers Medal for Distinguished Achievement in the Teaching of Electrical Engineering, 1960-10-10 (Bin 2, Frame 10)
  - John E. McKeen Distinguished Alumnus clipping, 1965-03-17 (Bin 2, Frame 11)
  - Distinguished Service Award, Transportation Research Board/National Research Council/National Academy of Sciences, 1977-01-26 (Bin 2, Frame 12)
  - The American Society for Engineering Education Hall of Fame Induction, 1993 (Bin 2, Frame 13)
  - The Better Brooklyn Committee Citation in Recognition of Outstanding Service in the Field of Science, 1965-11-18 (Bin 2, Frame 14)
  - The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) Education Society Achievement Award (Bin 2, Frame 15)
  - The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Microwave Theory and Techniques Society 1977 Microwaves Career Award, 1978-06-28 (Bin 2, Frame 16)
  - Long Island Technology Hall of Fame award, 2005-03-09 (Bin 2, Frame 17)
- Series III: Shelf 3, 2007
  - Harry S. Rogers Portrait, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 1)
  - Growth of the Future - Innovation Meets Art (Alfonso), 2007 (Bin 3, Frame 2)
  - Synergy - Innovation Meets Art (Samalot), 2007 (Bin 3, Frame 3)
  - Dr. Harry Stanley Rogers Plaque, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 4)
  - Harry S. Rogers Portrait, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 5)
  - David H. Cochran Library Portrait, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 6)
  - Unknown portrait, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 7)
  - Map Carte Du Canal Royal De La Province De Languedoc, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 8)
  - In Memory of Those Students Whose Lives Were Untimely Lost While Enrolled at Polytechnic Institute of New York, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 9)
  - The Society of the Sigma Xi, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 10)
  - Frank Rudolf Stamer Diploma from Poly, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 11)
  - Photograph of MetroTech dig, Undated (Bin 3, Frame 12)
- Series IV: Shelf 4, Undated
  - Navy blue banner, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 1)
  - Engineering inventions timelines collage, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 2)
  - Unknown portrait, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 3)
  - Unknown portrait, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 4)
  - S.A.T.C. Unit Photograph, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 5)
  - Space Shuttle Discovery Banner, Undated (Bin 4, Frame 6)
- Series V: Shelf 5, 1848-1987
  - Image of soldiers, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 1)
  - Map of China, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 2)
  - Framed butterfly, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 3)
  - Half-Million Miler 100,000 Mile Club, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 4)
  - The Cortelyou Mansion House Drawing, 1848 (Bin 5, Frame 5)
  - The New Institute Building Painting, 1890 (Bin 5, Frame 6)
  - Prof Ddr. Hermann Mark, 1987-01-25 (Bin 5, Frame 7)
  - Distinguished Leadership Award, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 8)
  - Telecommunications, Politics, Economics, and National Sovereignty, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 9)
  - National Research Council, Undated (Bin 5, Frame 10)
- Series VI: Shelf 6, 1976-2011
  - "Mastermind of Poly" Brooklyn Progress Article Framed, 1990-09 (Bin 6, Frame 1)
  - Lighthouse photograph, Undated (Bin 6, Frame 2)
  - Russian Counterterrorism Certificate, 2003-03-18 (Bin 6, Frame 3)
  - 9/11 NY Thanks Poly Photo, 2001-09-11 (Bin 6, Frame 4)
  - Brooklyn President Proclamation, 2011-04-27 (Bin 6, Frame 5)
  - UIC Distinguished Lecturer Series on Future Technological Challenges Poster, 2000-02-22 (Bin 6, Frame 6)
  - Universita Degli Studi Di Roma La Sapienza, Undated (Bin 6, Frame 7)
  - Lifetime National Associate of the National Academies, 2001-12 (Bin 6, Frame 8)
  - Long Island Forum for Technology Article, 1976-08-04 (Bin 6, Frame 9)
  - Pan American Foundation of Engineering Societies Distinction, 2008-12 (Bin 6, Frame 10)
  - Framed George Bugliarello Photograph, Undated (Bin 6, Frame 11)
  - Resolution of Appreciation, Undated (Bin 6, Frame 12)
  - National Academy of Engineering Distinguished Service, 1993-05-06 (Bin 6, Frame 13)
  - National Association for Science, Technology and Society, 1995-03-04 (Bin 6, Frame 14)
- Series VII: Shelf 7, 2001
  - SL1010 First-Year Student Project Fall 2001 In Remembrance of September 11, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 1)
  - SL1010 First-Year Student Project Fall 2001 In Remembrance of September 11, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 2)
  - Student Project 1, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 3)
  - Student Project 2, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 4)
  - Student Project 3, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 5)
  - Student Project 4, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 6)
  - Student Project 5, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 7)
  - Student Project 6, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 8)
  - Student Project 7, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 9)
  - Student Project 8, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 10)
  - Student Project 9, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 11)
  - Student Project 10, 2001 (Bin 7, Frame 12)
  - NYU Poly Marketing "Fuel", Undated (Bin 7, Frame 13)
  - NYU Poly Marketing, Undated (Bin 7, Frame 14)
- Series VIII: Shelf 8, 1864-1996
  - Hultin Pentagon Renovation Plaque, 1998-02-12 (Bin 8, Frame 1)
  - Joseph J. Jacobs Diploma, 1957 (Bin 8, Frame 2)
  - 83rd Annual Alumni Dinner Photograph, 1946 (Bin 8, Frame 3)
  - Dinner in Honor of Dr. Parke Kolbe Photograph, 1926 (Bin 8, Frame 4)
  - B.C.P.I Photograph, 1982 (Bin 8, Frame 5)
  - Mayor of New York Proclamation, 1990-11 (Bin 8, Frame 6)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair Drawing, 1864 (Bin 8, Frame 7)
  - Black and White Photograph of Building, Undated (Bin 8, Frame 8)
  - Black and White Photograph of Trees, Undated (Bin 8, Frame 9)
  - Black and White Photograph of Bells, Undated (Bin 8, Frame 10)
  - Black and White Photograph of Donkey, Undated (Bin 8, Frame 11)
- Series IX: Shelf 9, Undated
  - Astronaut Portrait: Lee Morin, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 1)
  - Astronaut Portrait: Charles Camarda, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 2)
  - Astronaut Portrait: Paolo Nespoli, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 3)
  - Library Portrait of David Chang, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 4)
  - Library Portrait of Ernst Weber, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 5)
  - Library Portrait of Arthur Grad, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 6)
  - Library Portrait of Harry S. Rogers, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 7)
  - Library Portrait of Parke Rexford Kolbe, Undated (Bin 9, Frame 8)
- Series X: Shelf 10, 1864-1973
  - Benjamin Alder Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 1)
  - Arthur Grad Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 2)
  - Erich Hausman Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 3)
  - Norman P. Auburn Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 4)
  - Edward J. Squire Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 5)
  - Irwin Henry Fenn Portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 6)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair Drawing, 1864 (Bin 10, Frame 7)
  - Unknown portrait, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 8)
  - Joseph Deitch Appreciation from Mayor Lindsay, 1973 (Bin 10, Frame 9)
  - Howard H. Blonder Diploma, 1961-06-14 (Bin 10, Frame 10)
  - Amerigo S. Costagliola Diploma, 1952-06-11 (Bin 10, Frame 10)
  - Library Portrait of John Howard Raymond, Undated (Bin 10, Frame 12)
- Series XI: Shelf 11, Undated
  - Library Portrait of Frederick Washington Atkinson, Undated (Bin 11, Frame 1)
  - Library Portrait of George Bugliarello, Undated (Bin 11, Frame 2)
  - Library Portrait of Jerry Hutlin, Undated (Bin 11, Frame 3)
  - Library Portrait of Katepalli Sreenivasan, Undated (Bin 11, Frame 4)